[{"answer": "I'm sorry. Will you excuse me", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Are you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " You are not from the area, are you", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "This is my estate", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I remember reading they ate a lot of squab", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " I don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "He's exactly like his name", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Several courses are served. Menus are often prepared days in advance, timed to perfection. It is said, without the culinary art, the crudeness of reality would make life unbearable", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " In that place", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What is it?", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "No, but I believe there is a rule that says everyone has to have HEARD of it", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "CHARLES, could you help me with the dessert in the kitchen", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "IN the kitchen. Excuse us", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Do I look THIRTY to you", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "You chose it specifically opposed to a lower number", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " It is", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I've got the muusic in me", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well? Let's see... I guess we could start by removing that great big stick from up your... Let's start with your walk", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You don't walk right.  You strut", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I understand", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Of course not. Let's go inside", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "that place up", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "that place up", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "How are ya", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "As I see it, the girl hasn't an inkling of your intentions. And it's no wonder. You, my friend, are a Merry my friend", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "A Merry my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You said my friend", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yes you did. Didn't he say my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "She has trouble with men, you know", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "She has met the right one. HUNDREDS of times. But she pulls back. She cuts herself off. You turn around and suddenly you're dating a Sphinx", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That must be him", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Blind date", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Cad. I can spot one a mile away.  I shall escort you out myself. I will act as your chaperone", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It is no trouble", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Yeah, it was. The harder I tried, the more persistent he became. He's conceited and inflated and unseasoned and it doesn't seem to matter... He's 134 years old but I can't get him out of my head", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Right here. Larger than life", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Do you miss him", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I think you are a remarkable woman my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I will have to have a talk with her", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend..", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Relationships these days are much more complicated than that. Women today have certain freedoms that men have been taking advantage of for centuries. You must have been aware of that. If you think about it clearly, it should be obvious to you that marriage between us is out of the question", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " Don't ever think that..", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Try our fragrance? Would you like to try our new fragrance today", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "It is called, POISON", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I'd be with you", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Just ask me... Just ask", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Oh, my", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "See that you do", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "my friend you don't have to holler like that. I'm not deaf..", "docId": "Kate-&-Leopold.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "...my friend?", "qsentId": 52}]